

## CONTACT

osmanmedoff@gmail.com



Osman Mammedov



Retropaint

## SKILLS

Javascript, Typescript	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$
Angular & Ionic	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$
Git (Github, Bitbucket)	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$
Laravel, MySQL	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$
Arduino	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$
Linux	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$
C, C++	••••
SFML	••000
CMake	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$ $\circ$
Docker	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$ $\circ$
Music Composition (Beepbox)	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$
Polyphone (Soundfront Editor)	••••

## REFERENCES

## **Dovlet Nazarov**

O CTO at Stampede Design

dov@stampede-design.com

#### HOBBIES

Programming (Native App Development)

Exploring & learning computer science skills

Composing music

# OSMAN MAMMEDOV

DEVELOPER

#### PROFILE

3 years of professional proficiency in frontend web technology, with a bit of experience in backend and dev-ops. In my free time, I like to mess around with compiled languages like Go or Rust, and other technologies like Docker or VPS services like DigitalOcean.

# EDUCATION

- Hibiscus International School (1st to 8th grade) | 2011 2018 | Malaysia
- Semesta Bilingual Boarding School (9th 12th grade) | 2018-2022 | Indonesia

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# Stampede Design

### Intern (Part-time)

March 2021 - April 2022

- · Developed web and mobile applications tailored to client requirements, utilizing Angular (HTML, CSS, Typescript) & Ionic framework technologies, with wide user bases of 500+ users.
- Utilized version control systems like Git (through Github Desktop & Sourcetre to manage and track changes to codebases of meduim to large sizes, collaborating effectively with team members on project development.
- Collaborated with backend developers to seamlessly integrate front-end code with server-side logic and databases, ensuring robust and efficient application functionality.

# **Front-End Developer**

April 2022 - Present

- Collaborated closely with UI/UX designers to translate design concepts into functional prototypes within practical boundaries, ensuring seamless user experiences across web and mobile platforms.
- · Worked in tandem with back-end developers to integrate front-end code with server-side logic and databases, contributing to full-stack development projects of small to medium sizes.
- · Implemented responsive design techniques to optimize web pages for various screen sizes and devices (from mobile to desktop), enhancing accessibility and user engagement.
- · Conducted comprehensive testing and debugging of front-end code to identify and resolve bugs and other issues, ensuring high-quality deliverables.
- Documented code and development processes to facilitate knowledge sharing and future maintenance, ensuring project scalability and continuity.
- · Identified and implemented performance optimizations to enhance the loading times and overall performance of web applications (up to 30%), improving user satisfaction and retention.